IVA JURKOVIC

20 Newport Parkway, Jersey City, NJ 07310 312-929-9137

ijurkovi@hawk.iit.edu

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/ivajurkovic/

OVERVIEW

A highly motivated recent graduate with previous work experience. Reliable employee with excellent work-ethic, who strives for excellence. Team-oriented with the ability to develop and implement ideas. Consistently recognized for excellent problem solving and analytical skills by supervisors. A results-oriented and solution-focused individual. Dedicated to continuing professional and educational development.

EDUCATION

ILLINOIS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, Chicago, IL

2014

B.S. in Business Administration: Finance. GPA: 3.91 /4.00

- . Dean's List for five semesters
- Presidential Scholarship, 2011 2014
- Relevant Course work: Intro to Computer Programming C++, Financial and Managerial Accounting, Corporate Finance, International Finance, Futures, Options, and Other Derivatives, Valuation/Portfolio Management
- Master of Science in Finance courses taken as an undergrad: Financial Statements Analysis, Financial Modeling, Mathematics with Financial Applications, Statistical Analysis in Financial Markets

HAROLD WASHINGTON COLLEGE - City Colleges of Chicago, Chicago, IL

2011

Associate in Science. GPA: 4.00/4.00

- Completed 41 credits toward Associate, transfer degree
- · President's List for three semesters
- Relevant Coursework: Macroeconomics, Microeconomics

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FOREX CAPITAL MARKETS, New York, NY

March 2015 - Present

Compliance Associate, Audits and Examinations – Full time position

- Assisting with critical communication and interaction between regulatory agencies and the company, as well as between internal/external auditors
- Collecting and analyzing data for regulatory and audit inquiries
- Setting up and executing continuous monitoring programs to ascertain the strength of the firm's internal controls and ensure adherence to applicable laws and regulations.
- Automating monitoring reports
- Documenting testing and the result of monitoring program
- Following up with relevant business units to ensure that remediation action is taken when necessary
- · Performing special projects as needed

V3 MARKETS LLC, Chicago, IL

May 2014 - February 2015

Financial Analyst – Full time position

- Performed trade and position reconciliation, and worked with clearing houses and traders to amend any breaks in timely and efficient manner
- Performed daily P&L reconciliation and reporting
- Improved Internal P&L accuracy
- · Monitored and maintained pricing and other reference data
- Modeled process for accurate booking of all relative trading fees
- Performed analysis of fee and brokerage charges that up to date resulted in collection of about \$35,000 overcharges.
- Collaborated with software developers in automating reconciliation processes and reporting through technology

INFINIUM CAPITAL MANAGEMENT, Chicago, IL

March 2013 - April

2014

QA Analyst - Intern

- Tested wide range of proprietary trading software
- Developed, documented, and improved total of 17 test plans to enhance their repeatability
- Created over 150 test cases with average test case effectiveness of about 67%
- Performed integration, system, acceptance, regression, compatibility testing
- Exceled in finding, documenting, and reporting bugs, errors, interoperability flaws and other issues within the proprietary software in order to optimize the trading strategies
- Researched compliance issues and aligning the current system implementation with exchange and other regulatory agencies' requirements
- Provided user training and support

CONSULATE GENERAL OF REPUBLIC OF CROATIA, Chicago, IL

Office Assistant – Summer position

- Performed administrative duties
- Performed data entry
- Conducted economic and political research

SKILLS

Computer: Proficient in MS Office (Excel, PowerPoint, Word), basic knowledge of Linux, T-SQL, SQL Server, SSIS , VBA, basic knowledge of C++, Gretl, Wireshark, Perforce, Jira, AutoCAD, Quicken Language: Fluent in English, Croatian, basic knowledge of Spanish and German

May 2011 - August 2011

ACTIVITIES/AFFILIATIONS

Stuart School Investment Club - performing fundamental stock analysis, covering energy sector CME Group Trading Challenge, 2013 and 2014
Wall Street Training Competition, 2012
Beta Gama Sigma, honor society for Business Schools, member since May 2013

Phi Theta Kappa, honor society, member since April 2011

National Society of Leadership and Success, member since September 2011